pennyauctionwatch.com 2012-12-14

# Privacy Policy & Terms – Penny Auction Watch®

**Warning** : Missing argument 2 for wpdb::prepare(), called in /home/pennyauc/public_html/wp-content/plugins/sharebar/sharebar.php on line 112 and defined in **/home/pennyauc/public_html/wp-includes/wp-db.php** on line **990**

**Warning** : Missing argument 2 for wpdb::prepare(), called in /home/pennyauc/public_html/wp-content/plugins/sharebar/sharebar.php on line 124 and defined in **/home/pennyauc/public_html/wp-includes/wp-db.php** on line **990**

This is the web site of **Penny Auction Watch**. **  
** We can be reached via e-mail at admin[at]pennyauctionwatch[dot]com

**General**

We may amend this Privacy Policy at any time by posting the amended terms on this site. All amended terms automatically take effect immediately.

**Use of your Personal Information**

Personal information provided by you as part of the subscription process, or otherwise, is used to operate the Site, manage your subscription and deliver the services you have requested. We may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of important changes to the Site and its functionality, other products or services available from our affiliates and us and, from time to time, to contact you on behalf of external business partners about a particular offering that may be of interest to you. 

For each visitor to PennyAuctionWatch.com, our Web server automatically recognizes only the user’s domain name, but not the e-mail address (where possible).

We collect the e-mail addresses as well as IP addresses of those who post messages to our bulletin board, the e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail, information volunteered by the user, such as survey information and/or site registrations.

**We have had problems with auction owners pretending to be winners of their own penny auction, as well as cases with owners shill bidding their auction site. If we find that you are posting false or misleading information and are affiliated with a penny auction business and trying to post and join our website under pseduonyms to defraud people and make people think that you are running a legitimate auction site by saying that you won things or for any other reason, your information will be made public and possibly sent to authorities or used in a legal case against you. This site was set up to keep people from being scammed by fake penny auction websites. For this reason information that you provide to us when you register or send e-mails to us may be disclosed if need be.  
**

We keep track of the Web sites and pages our customers visit via or within the Site, in order to determine which of our sites and services are the most popular. This data is used to deliver customized content and advertising.

When you enter our Site, we use your internet protocol (IP) address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer the Site and to help identify you. We also have the ability to know what type of operating system and browser software you use and to identify the geographical location of your browser. Your IP address is also used by us to gather broad demographic information and other purposes, such as monitoring visitor frequency.

The information we collect is used to improve the content of our Web page, disclosed when legally required to do so, at the request of governmental authorities conducting an investigation, to verify or enforce compliance with the policies governing our Website and applicable laws or to protect against misuse or unauthorized use of our Website.

### Public Forums and User Submissions

Penny Auction Watch is not responsible for any material submitted to the public areas by you (which include bulletin boards, hosted pages, chat rooms, or any other public area found on the website. Any material (whether submitted by you or any other user) is not endorsed, reviewed or approved by  Penny Auction Watch. Penny Auction Watch reserves the right to remove any material submitted or posted by you in the public areas, without notice to you, if it becomes aware and determines, in its sole and absolute discretion that you are or there is the likelihood that you may, including but not limited to -

**1** defame, abuse, harass, stalk, threaten or otherwise violate the rights of other users or any third parties;

**2** publish, post, distribute or disseminate any defamatory, obscene, indecent or unlawful material or information;

**3** post or upload files that contain viruses, corrupted files or any other similar software or programmes that may damage the operation of the Website Owner’s and/or a third party’s computer system and/or network;

**4** violate any copyright, trade mark, other applicable **US** or international laws or intellectual property rights of the Website Owner or any other third party;

**5** submit contents containing marketing or promotional material which is intended to solicit business.

**Materials You Provide; Account Use; Privacy**. For materials you post or otherwise provide to PennyAuctionWatch or in connection with the Services (your “Submission”), you grant PennyAuctionWatch  an irrevocable, perpetual, worldwide license to (1) use, copy, distribute, transmit, publicly display, publicly perform, reproduce, edit, modify, and translate your Submission, in connection with the Services or in any other media, and (2) sublicense these rights, to the maximum extent permitted by applicable law. PennyAuctionWatch  will not pay you for your Submission. PennyAuctionWatch  may remove your Submission at any time. For each Submission, you represent that you have all rights necessary to grant PennyAuctionWatch the rights in this paragraph. You may not share your PennyAuctionWatch  user account with others. You are responsible for all actions taken via your account. PennyAuctionWatch will treat your use of the Services in accordance with its Privacy Policy.

**Voluntary Information**

PennyAuctionWatch.com may, occasionally, ask you for further information about you as part of online surveys or if you enter any competition, contest or promotional feature.  

**Use of Cookies**  

We use “cookies” to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the Web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize our pages, or register with the Site, a cookie helps us to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This saves you time and simplifies your use of the Site. When you return to the Site, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the features that you customized.Â  No personally identifiable information is collected through the use of cookies.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the Site.

**Your information**

Your comments and forum posts, once you post them become property of this site.

**Sharing of Information with Third Parties  
**  
PennyAuctionWatch.com contains links to other websites, and you should be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices on any other website.

**With respect to Ad Servers:** To try and bring you offers that are of interest to you, we use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to our users based on your visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

The cookies of other [third-party vendors or ad networks](https://www.google.com/adsense/support/bin/answer.py?answer=94149) may also be used to serve ads on our site.

Upon request we provide site visitors with access to communications that the user/visitor has directed to our site (e.g., e-mails, customer inquiries). 

**Use of Data by Google- Google Analytics**

PennyAuctionWatch.com website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc.  Google Analytics uses cookies, which are text files placed on your computer, to help the website analyze how users use the site. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the website (including your IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the website, compiling reports on website activity for website operators and providing other services relating to website activity and internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google’s behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google.  You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings on your browser, however please note that if you do this you may not be able to use the full functionality of this website. By using this website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

**Contact Us  
**

* Send an e-mail to us at admin[at]pennyauctionwatch.com  
* Visit our URL at www.pennyauctionwatch.com
